<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<headers>
	
	<title>INSIGHTS - A NEW EXPERIENCE</title>
	<content>Open a new world of fresh experiences with MASH. With a plethora of features and security assured, breathe a new life into your device. Scroll down to explore more!</content>
	
	<title>Customize</title>
	<content>
		With an open OS, you’re in control. You have more freedom and more choices, from the big picture down to the smallest details. Your mobile experience should be as unique as you. 
	</content>
	
	<title>Mods Integration </title>
	<content>
		The post-app era is now redundant. Enter Mods. Mods are intelligent, aware, and lightweight experiences built directly into the OS. MASH is Mod ready, which means it has all those functionalities that set the ROM apart from industry standards. Just saying. 
	</content>

	<title>Per-app Theming </title>
	<content>
		 MASH offers customisation at the deepest levels. From system apps to various third party applications, theme each and every aspect of the system. Make it yours, We've got your back. 
	</content>

	<title>Better Audio </title>
	<content>
		AudioFX gives you unmatched customization and quality for your music. AudioFX delivers 24-bit High-Res Lossless Audio with bass boost, surround, reverb, and 13 preset configurations. Sounds good? 
	</content>

	<title>Privacy and Security </title>
	<content>
		Privacy Guard helps you understand exactly what your device is revealing to the world—so you can have total control over what is shared. While PIN Scramble randomizes the numbers behind your PIN every time. You never have to worry about someone spying on your PIN strokes or reconstructing your PIN from smudges on your screen.
	</content>

	<title>Less Spam, More Connected  </title>
	<content>
		Use Blocked Caller List to permanently block any numbers you wish from ever calling or texting your device again. Plus, with more than 1.7 billion contacts worldwide, the robust caller ID included in Truecaller Integrated Dialer allows you to identify and block incoming spam right from your heads up notification.
	</content>

</headers>